Alright, you're done. Let's start by uncommenting out that text.
As you can see, you need that four cast string
to pass on to our detail activity. So what do
we use to get that four cast string? Well we're lucky
here, because we actually get the adapter view cast in.
All we have to do is cast it at simple
cursor adaptor and then we can get the cursor. We
can move it to our position. Then, we can use string.format
to get a formatted string based on the values
of our columns. Note, once again the nice use
of our column intendacies. One ending curly brace and
let's move that intend stuff into there. And that's it.
Now we'll be able to click on it again
and it'll actually go to our normal detail view.
Let's try it out. So here we are, there's
our list view and we go right into details. Pretty
cool. However, if we change our temperature units to imperial here
doesn't actually update. It would be nice if that, it was
based on the same kind of cursor model we have here.
Something that was observing with the
content observer and would actually update.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
When we changed our setting.